<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/sumo-documentation/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/sumo-documentation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-05-27T07:07:37+00:00</updated><id>/sumo-documentation/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Eclipse SUMO - Documentation</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here 12345. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="/sumo-documentation/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2019-05-24T11:40:08+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-24T11:40:08+00:00</updated><id>/sumo-documentation/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/sumo-documentation/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Installing</title><link href="/sumo-documentation/welcome-to-jekyll2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Installing" /><published>2019-05-24T11:40:08+00:00</published><updated>2019-05-24T11:40:08+00:00</updated><id>/sumo-documentation/welcome-to-jekyll2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/sumo-documentation/welcome-to-jekyll2.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;windows&quot;&gt;Windows&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are four different binary packages for Windows depending on the platform (32 vs. 64 bit) you have and what you want to do with SUMO. If you want to install it locally and have administrator rights on your machine you should download and execute one of the installers (preferably 64 bit). If you need a “portable” version or do not have admin rights, use the correct zip, extract it into a desired folder using &lt;a href=&quot;http://7-zip.de/&quot;&gt;7Zip&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.winzip.de/prod_down.htm&quot;&gt;Winzip&lt;/a&gt;, or a similar tool. Every package contains the binaries, all dlls needed, the examples, tools, and documentation in HTML format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download 64 bit installer: &lt;a href=&quot;http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/sumo/sumo-win64-1.2.0.msi?download&quot;&gt;sumo-win64-1.2.0.msi&lt;/a&gt;
Download 64 bit zip: &lt;a href=&quot;http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/sumo/sumo-win64-1.2.0.zip?download&quot;&gt;sumo-win64-1.2.0.zip&lt;/a&gt;
Download 32 bit installer: &lt;a href=&quot;http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/sumo/sumo-win32-1.2.0.msi?download&quot;&gt;sumo-win32-1.2.0.msi&lt;/a&gt;
Download 32 bit zip: &lt;a href=&quot;http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/sumo/sumo-win32-1.2.0.zip?download&quot;&gt;sumo-win32-1.2.0.zip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the installation folder, you will find a folder named &lt;strong&gt;“bin”&lt;/strong&gt;. Here, you can find the executables (programs). You may double click on SUMO-GUI and take a look at the examples located in &lt;strong&gt;docs/examples&lt;/strong&gt;. All other applications (DUAROUTER, DFROUTER, etc.) have to be run from the command line. To facilitate this there is also a start-commandline.bat which sets up the whole environment for you. If you feel unsure about the command line, please read Basics/Basic_Computer_Skills#Running_Programs_from_the_Command_Line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want a bleeding edge nightly build or need tests or source files, you can download them from the Download page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For building SUMO from source see building SUMO under Windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;linux&quot;&gt;Linux&lt;/h1&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Windows There are four different binary packages for Windows depending on the platform (32 vs. 64 bit) you have and what you want to do with SUMO. If you want to install it locally and have administrator rights on your machine you should download and execute one of the installers (preferably 64 bit). If you need a “portable” version or do not have admin rights, use the correct zip, extract it into a desired folder using 7Zip, Winzip, or a similar tool. Every package contains the binaries, all dlls needed, the examples, tools, and documentation in HTML format.</summary></entry></feed>